[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi", "Obama"], "LOCATION": ["London", "Bin Jawad", "Misrata"]}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "Is that the story of the day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "It's the story of the day and even bigger than that I think is the story that Gadhafi's response to the conference in London, to President Obama's speech, is the go on the offensive not just against the rebels in the east, around Bin Jawad, and all that territory they took around the oil fields over the last few days, but also in the town of Misrata where we visited just yesterday, going on the offensive there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Not just Twitter but Facebook and other mediums of that type?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "What we've heard in all these countries is that the people have lost the fear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Benghazi"], "PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "So what does stopped in the tracks mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "What it means, Piers, is that as you well know when the coalition military activity began some 10 days ago, it occurred just as Gadhafi's forces were massing on the strategic city in the east of Benghazi where some 700,000 people were very vulnerable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "So can you clarify it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "It's really -- it's really not that confusing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Will you be arming -- will you be arming the rebels, Ambassador?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "We will -- as I was just getting to, we'll be providing political, humanitarian, other forms of assistance to the opposition.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "What's your -- what's your name on twitter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "@AmbassadorRice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "DT", ",", "RB", "CD", "DT", ",", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "And what do you think of the power of Twitter in terms of what we've seen in the Middle East in particular where you have young, educated people using Twitter and other social networking means to spread the message from these countries in the way they perhaps wouldn't have been able to 10, 15 years ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "NNS", "VBG", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Well, it certainly has dramatically changed the way that people can communicate with one another, rally one another, to common objectives.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Did you ever imagine in your wildest dreams that you would have that kind of spread?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "It's extremely humbling to see how quickly the velocity of the service, how it's taken off.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Was that part of the thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "So it's always been focused on the recipient.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mubarak"], "LOCATION": ["Egypt", "Tahrir Square"]}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", ":", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "How dramatically has this changed your working practice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, it means that -- for example, in Egypt -- so when I go to Tahrir Square, as you know I did during the protests, and I see a thug sent by Mubarak, one of these plainclothes policemen carrying this big club with nails embedded in it, then you know I don't wait to see what happens, I don't wait for -- until my next column.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Which is amazingly powerful firsthand immediate testimony, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Noah Glass"]}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Whose idea was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "It was one of our co-workers, Noah Glass.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Could you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "The bosses or Twitter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Well, actually that has come up a few times when I'm in some very dicey position, and I tweet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Because I've noticed it's a mixture of amusing stuff about you and your life, but primarily it's a fantastic business tool, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "It is very much so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "How vast is your audience at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Well, it's -- right now I have about 2.2 million followers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Does it show power and influence, the total?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "I don't think she's going to actually take over the presidency if she gets more followers than Obama.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "You become almost a -- in perpetuity publicist, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", ":", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Well, you could.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "What is a bad use of Twitter, particularly for famous people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Well, I don't know what a bad use it, because I have had only very, very good response to my tweets.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "While you're still -- are you still new to it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I'm a newbie, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Because you're of Polish descent, what is your favorite Polish dish that you like to cook?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "Pierogi.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Pierogi?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "And what is Pierogi?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "It's a dumpling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "That's tomorrow, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "It's tomorrow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBG", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "What's the persuasive element for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Well, I just got a whole lot of tweets from people saying -- I'm sure they're dictating the requests of their child or something, asking how difficult is it, it is very easy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Should you drink and tweet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Alyssa, this was a rather curious way to track your follower account up, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "That was a very proud Twitter moment for me, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Forget business for a moment, in terms of raising awareness of issues, charitable causes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Definitely, definitely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Did you have any -- any qualms about doing that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "ILANO: No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "We're all Twits, really, aren't we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "We're all Twits.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "WDT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "About stars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Actually, early on I didn't think celebrities would want to use Twitter because I thought for exactly that reason, that part of their allure was that you couldn't get close to them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "I want to see -- Martha, you got any good Tweets?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Here's a good one.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Martha"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "And in contrast to poor old Mayor Bloomberg, who was getting booted all around New York by the media because he had the gall to spend 48 hours without solving it, which in Britain would have taken three years -- you were getting all the praise because you hit the Twitter and you were just talking directly to people trapped in the snow, weren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Well, every mayor was struggling in this area.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mayor Bloomberg"], "LOCATION": ["New York", "Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["March", "May of '09"]}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "When did you realize this was going to be a really effective tool for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "I got on in March -- May of '09.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Did you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Is that what you want to see happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "I hope so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Pretty extraordinary, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "It's amazing what people are doing with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Would you like to see the president being more pro- active on Twitter himself, actually doing what you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "JJR", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "I don't know if it's practical there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "What do you think about the role of Twitter in creating talented leaders in U.S. politics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Well, you know, I think that leaders need to be accessible.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "When you have your baby, will you be putting the first baby pictures proudly up on your Twitter, Tweeting to the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "ILANO: I don't know about baby pictures, because then that becomes a security issue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "That's the definition of obsessive junkie, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "You see it as a really great business tool, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Yeah, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Who wants to see that all way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "We've talked about this before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "Can you get a little bit too fresh on Twitter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "Well, it's a public medium.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "What is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "Square.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "What do I do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "I can swipe your card right here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]